### Personal Data Protection

##### Principles of Processing Personal Data

Principles of processing personal data (Privacy Policy) describe how SK ensures the protection of personal data in accordance with applicable laws.

**Version 7.0** / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/SK-POPPD-EN-CURRENT.pdf) (ENG) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/SK-POPPD-ET-CURRENT.pdf) (EST) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/SK-POPPD-LT-CURRENT.pdf) (LT) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/SK-POPPD-LV-CURRENT.pdf) (LV) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/SK-POPPD-RU-CURRENT.pdf) (RUS) / valid from 10.10.2022

**Authorized processors of personal data** [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Authorized-processors-of-personal-data.pdf) (ENG) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Volitatud-tootlejate-list.pdf) (EST)

Version 6.0 / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/SK-POPPD-EN-v6.pdf) (ENG) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/SK-POPPD-ET-v6_0.pdf) (EST) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/SK-POPPD-LT-V_6_0.pdf) (LT) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/SK-POPPD-LV-6_0.pdf) (LV) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/SK-POPPD-RU-v6_0.pdf) (RUS) / valid from 28.09.2020

Version 5.0 / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/SK-POPPD-EN-v5.pdf) (ENG) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/SK-POPPD-ET-v5.pdf) (EST) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/SK-POPPD-LT-v5.pdf) (LT) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/SK-POPPD-LV-v5.pdf) (LV) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/SK-POPPD-RU-v5.pdf) (RUS) / valid from 05.12.2019  
Version 4.0 / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/SK-Principles%20of%20Processing%20Personal%20Data%20v4_0_EN.pdf) (ENG) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/SK-isikuandmete%20t%C3%B6%C3%B6tlemise%20p%C3%B5him%C3%B5tted%20v4_0.pdf) (EST) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/SK-Principles%20of%20Processing%20Personal%20Data%20v4_0_LT.pdf) (LT) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/SK-Principles%20of%20Processing%20Personal%20Data%20v4_0_LV.pdf) (LV) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/SK-Principles%20of%20Processing%20Personal%20Data%20v4_0_RU.pdf) (RUS) / valid from 10.12.2018  
Version 3.0 / [PDF](https://www.sk.ee/upload/files/SK-Principles%20of%20Processing%20Personal%20Data%20v3_0.pdf) (ENG) / [PDF](https://www.sk.ee/upload/files/SK-isikuandmete%20t%C3%B6%C3%B6tlemise%20p%C3%B5him%C3%B5tted%20v3_0.pdf) (EST) / valid from 25.05.2018  
Version 2.0 / [PDF](https://www.sk.ee/upload/files/SK-Principles%20of%20Processing%20Personal%20Data-v2.pdf) (ENG) / [PDF](https://www.sk.ee/upload/files/SK-isikuandmete%20t%C3%B6%C3%B6tlemise%20p%C3%B5him%C3%B5tted-v2_0.pdf) (EST) / valid from 01.03.2018  
Version 1.0 / [PDF](https://www.sk.ee/upload/files/Principles%20of%20Client%20Data%20Protection_v1.pdf) (ENG) / [PDF](https://www.sk.ee/upload/files/Kliendiandmete%20kaitse%20p%C3%B5him%C3%B5tted.pdf) (EST) / valid from 22.12.2011

##### Consent for Automated Biometric Identity Verification

**Version 1.0** / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/ABIV-CONSENT-EN-CURRENT.pdf) (ENG) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/ABIV-CONSENT-ET-CURRENT.pdf) (EST) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/ABIV-CONSENT-LT-CURRENT.pdf) (LT) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/ABIV-CONSENT-LV-CURRENT.pdf) (LV) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/ABIV-CONSENT-RU-CURRENT.pdf) (RUS) / valid from 13.01.2020

##### Authentigate Service Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how SK ensures the protection of personal data while providing Authentigate Service.

**Version 1.0** / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/Authentigate_Service_Privacy_Policy.pdf) (ENG) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/Authentigate_Service_Privacy_Policy_ET_.pdf) (EST) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/Authentigate_Service_Privacy_Policy_LT.pdf) (LT) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/Authentigate_Service_Privacy_Policy_LV.pdf) (LV) / valid from 11.09.2024

##### Cookie Policies for websites

##### portal.skidsolutions.eu

[PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Principles-of-using-cookies-on-the-website-portal.skidsolutions.eu_ENG.pdf) (ENG)

##### myid.skidsolutions.eu

[PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/Principles%20of%20using%20cookies%20on%20the%20website%20myid_skidsolutions_eu_ENG.pdf) (ENG) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/K%C3%BCpsiste%20kasutamise%20p%C3%B5him%C3%B5tted%20veebilehel_MyID_EE.pdf) (EST) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/Slapuk%C5%B3%20politika%20interneto%20svetain%C4%97je_MyID_LT.pdf) (LT) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/myid_skidsolutions_eu%20t%C4%ABmek%C4%BCa%20vietnes%20s%C4%ABkfailu%20politika_LV.pdf) (LV) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/%D0%9F%D0%BE%D0%BB%D0%B8%D1%82%D0%B8%D0%BA%D0%B0%20%D0%B2%20%D0%BE%D1%82%D0%BD%D0%BE%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%BD%D0%B8%D0%B8%20%D1%84%D0%B0%D0%B9%D0%BB%D0%BE%D0%B2%20cookie%20%D0%BD%D0%B0%20%D0%B2%D0%B5%D0%B1-%D1%81%D0%B0%D0%B9%D1%82%D0%B5_MyID_RU%20.pdf) (RUS)

##### smart-id.com

[PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/Principles%20of%20using%20cookies%20on%20the%20website%20smart-id_com_ENG(2).pdf) (ENG) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/K%C3%BCpsiste%20kasutamise%20p%C3%B5him%C3%B5tted%20veebilehel%20smart-id_com_EE.pdf) (EST) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/Slapuk%C5%B3%20politika%20interneto%20svetain%C4%97je_smart-id_com_LT.pdf) (LT) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/Smart-id_com%20t%C4%ABmek%C4%BCa%20vietnes%20s%C4%ABkfailu%20politika_LV.pdf) (LV) / [PDF](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/upload/files/%D0%9F%D0%BE%D0%BB%D0%B8%D1%82%D0%B8%D0%BA%D0%B0%20%D0%B2%20%D0%BE%D1%82%D0%BD%D0%BE%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%BD%D0%B8%D0%B8%20%D1%84%D0%B0%D0%B9%D0%BB%D0%BE%D0%B2%20cookie%20%D0%BD%D0%B0%20%D0%B2%D0%B5%D0%B1-%D1%81%D0%B0%D0%B9%D1%82%D0%B5_smart-id_com_RU.pdf) (RUS)

Phone: [+372 610 1880](tel:+3726101880)  
E-mail: [info@skidsolutions.eu](mailto:info@skidsolutions.eu)

###### Company

###### Services

###### [Eesti keeles](https://skidsolutions.eu/eesti-keeles)

© 2001-2024 SK ID Solutions AS. All rights reserved. [Data Protection](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/resources/data-protection/) | [Copyright](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/resources/copyright/) | [Cookie Policy](https://www.skidsolutions.eu/resources/data-protection/)
